publishthis.com 2012-10-22

# Privacy Policy | PublishThis | Content Curation Platform

This Web Site is published and maintained by Ultra Unlimited, d/b/a PublishThis, located at:  
14431 Ventura Boulevard  
#302 Sherman Oaks, CA 91423

(“PublishThis”). PublishThis is referred to in this Privacy Policy as “we,” “us,” “our,” or other similar pronouns.

This Privacy Policy governs the information collection, use and disclosure practices of the **www.publishthis.com** web site (the “Web Site”). By visiting this Web Site, and/or using the services offered on or through this Web Site, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy as they may be amended from time to time. As we update and expand our services, this Privacy Policy may change, so check back to this page from time to time. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into, and part of, the [Web Site Terms of Use](http://www.publishthis.com/terms-of-use/ "Terms of Use"), which governs your use of this Web Site in general.

This Privacy Policy does not apply to information that you may provide to us, or that we may obtain, other than through our Web Site, such as by phone, through postal mail and through other live and print media.

This Web Site is intended for users who are located in the United States of America. This Privacy Policy shall be interpreted under the laws of the United States.

**Purpose**

The privacy of your information is important to us. In order to make your use of our Web Site as worthwhile as possible, we may collect Personal Information from and about you, and we may collect certain information from your computer about you and your visits to this Web Site. “ **Personal Information** ” includes, for example, your name; home and/or business address; e-mail address; telephone, wireless and/or fax number; and/or other information that may identify you as an individual or allow online or offline contact with you as an individual. This Privacy Policy explains, in general, what Personal Information and other information is collected on this Web Site, how the information is used, and with whom we may share such information.

**Right to Opt In and Opt Out**

You may have the right to “opt in” and “opt out” of certain of our uses of your Personal Information. For example, at the time you are requested to provide Personal Information on this Web Site, you may have the opportunity to elect to, or not to receive correspondence from us. You may also opt out of PublishThis’s promotional e-mails by clicking on an opt-out link within the e-mail you receive.

Please understand that if you opt out of receiving promotional correspondence from us, we may still contact you in connection with your relationship, activities, transactions and communications with us.

**What Information is Collected on this Web Site?**

**User-Provided Information**

We collect Personal Information from users of our Web Site, for example, through such users’ activities, transactions and completion of online forms on our Web Site. Such information is also collected, for example, when users submit a comment or question to us using a “contact us” or similar feature on our Web Site, send us an e-mail, or in any other way submit Personal Information to us via our Web Site.

You may be able to send information about our products and services to your friends and family members through our Web Site by clicking on an “E-mail to Friend” or similar button on our Web Site or in an e-mail that we have sent you. In some of these cases (unless you simply forward our e-mail on your own), you may provide the name and e-mail address of your friend or family member to us. Such information will be treated in accordance with this Privacy Policy and applicable law.

**Web Site Usage Information**

**Cookies**

We may use “cookies” to keep, and sometimes track, information about you. Cookies are small data files that are sent to your browser or related software from a Web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive. Cookies track where you travel on our Web Site. A cookie may enable us to relate your use of our Web Site to other information about you, including your Personal Information. All of these purposes serve to improve and personalize your experience on our Web Site.

Most Web browsers can be set to inform you when a cookie has been sent to you and provide you with the opportunity to refuse that cookie. Additionally, if you have a Flash player installed on your computer, your Flash player can be set to reject or delete Flash cookies. However, refusing a cookie may, in some cases, preclude you from using, or negatively impact the display or function of, the Web Site or certain areas or features of the Web Site.

**By using our Web Site, you consent to our use of cookies as described above.**

**Clear GIFs**

We may use “clear GIFs” (aka “Web beacons” or “pixel tags”) or similar technologies, in the Web Site and/or in our communications with you to enable us to know whether you have visited a Web page or received a message. A clear GIF is typically a one-pixel, transparent image (although it can be a visible image as well), located on a Web page or in an e-mail or other type of message, which is retrieved from a remote site on the Internet enabling the verification of an individual’s viewing or receipt of a Web page or message. A clear GIF may enable us to relate your viewing or receipt of a Web page or message to other information about you, including your Personal Information.

**IP Address and Clickstream Data**

Our server automatically collects data about your Internet address when you visit us. This information, known as an Internet Protocol address, or IP Address, is a number that’s automatically assigned to your computer by your Internet service provider whenever you’re on the Internet. Our server may also record the Web page from which you linked to this Web Site (e.g., another Web site or a search engine); the pages you visit on this Web Site; the Web site you visit after this Web Site; the ads you see and/or click on; other information about the type of Web browser, computer, platform, related software and settings you are using; any search terms you have entered on this Web Site or a referral site; and other Web usage activity and data logged by our Web servers. We use this information for internal system administration, to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web Site. Such information may also be used to gather broad demographic information, such as country of origin and Internet Service Provider. We may also link this information with your Personal Information.

Any or all of these activities with regard to Web Site Usage Information may be performed on our behalf by our services providers.

**How is the Personal Information used?**

We will use the Personal Information you provide to our Web Site, for example, to respond to your requests and to provide you with information about our product and service offerings. We may also use your Personal Information to maintain our internal record keeping. We may match information collected from you through different means or at different times, including both Personal Information and Web Site Usage Information, and use such information along with information obtained from other sources, including third parties.

In addition, we may send you notices (for example, in the form of e-mails, mailings, and the like), and otherwise correspond with you, about products, services, companies and events, sponsored by us and others, that we think might interest you. You may opt out of receiving such notices from us by following the instructions in the Right to Opt In and Opt Out section above.

We may analyze user behavior as a measure of interest in, and use of, our Web Site and e-mails, both on an individual basis and in the aggregate.

**Do we share Personal Information and Web Site Usage information with others?**

**Service Providers**

We may use third-party partners to help operate our Web Site and deliver our products and services, and may share your information with our service providers and other third parties that provide products or services for or through this Web Site or for our business (such as Web site or database hosting companies, address list hosting companies, e-mail service providers, analytics companies, distribution companies, fulfillment companies, and other similar service providers that use such information on our behalf).

Web Site Usage and other Non-Personally Identifiable Information  
We may disclose Web Site Usage Information and other non-personally identifiable information regarding our users and user behavior as a measure of interest in, and use of, our Web Site and e-mails to third parties, including, for example, aggregate data, such as overall patterns or demographic reports that do not describe or identify any individual user.

**Legal Disclosures**

We may disclose user information to government authorities, and to other third parties when compelled to do so by government authorities, at our discretion, or otherwise as required or permitted by law, including but not limited to in response to court orders and subpoenas. We also may disclose user information when we have reason to believe that someone is causing injury to or interference with our rights or property, other users of the Web Site, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities.

**Business Transfer**

In the event that PublishThis, any or substantially all of its assets, are acquired by one or more third parties as a result of an acquisition, merger, sale, reorganization, consolidation or liquidation, Personal Information may be one of the transferred assets.

**Wireless Addresses**

If the e-mail address you provide to us is a wireless e-mail address, you agree to receive messages at such address from COMPANY (unless and until you have elected not to receive such messages by following the instructions in the Right to Opt In and Opt Out section above). You understand that your wireless carrier’s standard rates apply to these messages, and that you may change your mind at any time by following the instructions in the Right to Opt In and Opt Out section above. You represent that you are the owner or authorized user of the wireless device on which messages will be received, and that you are authorized to approve the applicable charges.

**Your Access Rights**

You may review, update or modify the Personal Information that is stored in your user account on this Web Site by e-mailing support. If you send us requests via e-mail, before we are able to provide you with any information, correct any inaccuracies or delete any information, however, we may ask you to verify your identity and to provide other details to help us to respond to your request.

**Security**

While we endeavor to protect the security and integrity of sensitive Personal Information collected via this Web Site, due to the inherent nature of the Internet as an open global communications vehicle, we cannot guarantee that any information, during transmission through the Internet or while stored on our system or otherwise in our care, will be absolutely safe from intrusion by others, such as hackers.

If you contact us by e-mail or a “contact us” or similar feature on our Web Site, you should be aware that your transmission might not be secure. A third party could view information you send by these methods in transit.

We will have no liability for disclosure of your information due to errors or unauthorized acts of third parties during or after transmission.

**Consent to Processing**

By providing Personal Information to this Web Site, you consent to the collection, maintenance, processing and transfer of such information in and to the United States and other countries and territories, pursuant to the laws of the United States, which may provide lesser privacy protections than the laws of other countries.

**“Linked-To” Web Sites**

When you are on our Web Site you may have the opportunity to visit, or link to, other Web sites, including other Web sites operated by third parties. These sites may collect Personal Information about you. PublishThis does not control sites that are operated by these entities and is not responsible for the information practices of these sites. This Privacy Policy does not address the information practices of other Web sites.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy from time to time, and such changes will be effective immediately upon posting to this Web Site. Under certain circumstances (for example, in connection with certain material changes), we may also elect to notify you of changes or updates to our Privacy Policy, or to request your consent for such changes, by additional means, such as posting a notice on the front page of our Web Site to sending you an e-mail.

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions or comments regarding our privacy practices, you may [contact us.

**Effective Date: April 14th, 2012**
